<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Artists on So, How Is That Working For You?</title>
    <link>/artists/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Artists on So, How Is That Working For You?</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-GB</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/artists/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Abi Price</title>
      <link>/artists/abi-price/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artists/abi-price/</guid>
      <description>Abi Price is a computational artist and performer based in the UK. Her work includes installations, screen based generative art and the use of interactive technologies in performative settings. With a background in contemporary dance, she has created interdisciplinary performances, exploring the role of digital technologies within choreographic practice.
Her most recent interests involve the translation of screen based art into physical objects, as well as the use of computation to explore nature.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adam He</title>
      <link>/artists/adam-he/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artists/adam-he/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Andi Wang</title>
      <link>/artists/andi-wang/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artists/andi-wang/</guid>
      <description>Andi Wang is a creative technologist and a digital artist with a background of digital media art from China. Her previous work has used a variety of media, including animation, interactive installation, AR and VR, to present different types of artwork in this digital age. She is currently focusing on creating performance with projection mapping and computational technology. Her works try to explore a new format of dancing performance and bring a unique experience to the audience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ankita Anand</title>
      <link>/artists/ankita-anand/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artists/ankita-anand/</guid>
      <description>Ankita Anand is an Indian artist. Her background as an artist is in experimental moving image - where she combines documentary film and fiction to create surreal Narrations. In the past year her focus has moved on to creative coding and programming, in particular exploring places where spirituality and technology might overlap. The medium (performance, installation or video) is chosen by the intention of the work, creating a clear link between the two.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Annie Tådne</title>
      <link>/artists/annie-t%C3%A5dne/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artists/annie-t%C3%A5dne/</guid>
      <description>Annie Tådne works within the intersection of art and technology. Her work spans a diverse range of mediums and environments such as theatre, club culture, music and installation. Her interests lie in the synthesis of art, media, technology and architecture, where music is paramount in all of her creations. She explores spatial and embodied cognition through audiovisual and performative modes of expression. Lately, she has inquired into certain aspects of post-digitalism, where the combination of light, sound, space, materials, and structures can give new resonance to how we consider art and technology, and amplify the construction of a reality that is active, dynamic and co-evolutionary.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Baqi Ba</title>
      <link>/artists/baqi-ba/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artists/baqi-ba/</guid>
      <description>Baqi Ba’s work explores the screen as a boundary between reality and data system. Her work often takes on a political approach as a critique of human-machine generated systems especially the ‘circular causal’ relationship between them. Her medium of practice includes photography, film, installations and computational media. Baqi’s current area of interest is on expanded forms of cinema, focusing on the use of interactivity and immersive Narration in a short film.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Batool Desouky</title>
      <link>/artists/batool-desouky/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artists/batool-desouky/</guid>
      <description>Batool Desouky is an artist and art practitioner working with different forms of displacement, memory and the imagination, using Narration as a tool to create fabulations of times past, present and future.
Batool has worked as programme coordinator and curatorial assistant at Sharjah Art Foundation, UAE (2013 – 2018) during which we also maintained her art practice. Her work was exhibited as part of Collectivity: Objects and Associations in the UAE Art World, Maraya Art Centre, Sharjah (2018), Vantage Point Sharjah, Sharjah Art Foundation (2017), and took part in an online residency titled Residency For Artists On Hiatus (2014).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Benjamin Sammon</title>
      <link>/artists/benjamin-sammon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artists/benjamin-sammon/</guid>
      <description>Benjamin Sammon is an audio-visual artist with a background in music and video art. His areas of study mainly revolve around the aesthetics of failure and hauntology which both have a tendency to inform his artistic practice. Sammon’s interest is in making tactile performance devices that can be used as a part of a system to make music and visuals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bingxin Feng</title>
      <link>/artists/bingxin-feng/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artists/bingxin-feng/</guid>
      <description>Bingxin Feng is a multidisciplinary designer, interested in the effect of digital image on the experience of humanity. Her practice takes form through photography, film, animation and interactive experience design.
Bingxin graduated from London College of Communication Graphic and Media Design (2018), then carried out a design internship at SHOWstudio, a fashion communication studio lead by photographer Nick Knight, where she explored her passion for experimental moving images, fashion and technology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chris Speed</title>
      <link>/artists/chris-speed/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artists/chris-speed/</guid>
      <description>Chris Speed is an audio-visual artist and creative coder. His work explores abstraction as a tool for expression through both digital and analogue technology. Computer music is the other main passion in his life, being an experienced VJ for many international labels and collectives. He is currently based in London.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christina Karpodini</title>
      <link>/artists/christina-karpodini/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artists/christina-karpodini/</guid>
      <description>Christina Karpodini is a Greek composer, media artist, and singer, currently living in London. Her compositional practice focuses on electroacoustic compositions with synthesized sounds, pre-recorded sounds, and instruments. She is currently exploring interactive computational forms that would enable a better perception of electroacoustic music. Her musical education started at an early age with classical piano training and participation in vocal ensembles. She has graduated with the Diploma in Music Harmony from the conservatory in 2011 and with the Diploma in Counterpoint Music in 2013, both in Athens.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Claire Kwong</title>
      <link>/artists/claire-kwong/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artists/claire-kwong/</guid>
      <description>Claire Kwong makes interactive art to dramatize her personal experience with technology. She works with computation to create performances and interactive experiences. Kwong creates generative systems and improvises within them. She incorporates live controls, spontaneous movement, and audience interaction. Her recent work at Goldsmiths draws on her studies of game design and participatory art.
Before moving to London to study at Goldsmiths, Kwong lived and worked in New York City. There, she exhibited work at local venues including Babycastles and Harvestworks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Clemence Debaig</title>
      <link>/artists/clemence-debaig/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artists/clemence-debaig/</guid>
      <description>Clemence Debaig is a designer, dancer and computational artist, based in London. She enjoys solving problems for people, working with digital technology and creating interactive experiences. With a background in mechanical engineering, industrial design, user experience and contemporary dance, she has worked on many high profile projects, while maintaining an active practice as an artist and dancer.
She is interested in exploring how interactivity can make people dance and how digital technology can encourage audience participation during performances.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daniah Alsaleh</title>
      <link>/artists/daniah-alsaleh/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artists/daniah-alsaleh/</guid>
      <description>Daniah Alsaleh’s work tackles notions of the unobtrusive, the ordinary and the common. Her approach is to deconstruct and rearrange the obvious, to make the invisible visible, and manifest a space for reflection with new ways of seeing. She uses geometry and pattern making in her form of expression by mixing tangible and intangible objects of art, crossing disciplines from traditional mediums of painting to developing generative art processes with code.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>David Williams</title>
      <link>/artists/david-williams/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artists/david-williams/</guid>
      <description>David Williams works with various non-human entities to explore networked relationships, world sharing and other-consciouness. His work speculates on notions of panpsychism and (inter)agency through performance, sound and visualization.
David has a background in art and music, graduating in 2010 with an undergraduate degree in Fine Art from Cardiff Metropolitan University. Originally from Wales, David is now based in London, UK.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dongyuan Liu</title>
      <link>/artists/dongyuan-liu/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artists/dongyuan-liu/</guid>
      <description>Dongyuan Liu is new media artist, whose work primarily focuses on new media art performance and installation art. His previous work uses different media in early works, such as interactive installation, audio-visual, animation, video and so on. In the past year, he has used more technical means to create works related to new media art performances and immersive experiences. He tried to combine new media art with traditional art and explore his own new artistic symbols.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eddie Wong</title>
      <link>/artists/eddie-wong/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artists/eddie-wong/</guid>
      <description>Eddie Wong is a creative technologist who works with Narration as a material. Coming from a background in animation, he understands the importance of bringing forth ordinary human stories that may otherwise be subsumed under the grand Narrations of history and power. Eddie intervenes in technologies to counteract the singular Narrations that have come to shape the data-hungry, post-truth world. He’s interested in presenting alternative viewpoints to the artificial intelligence hype by co-opting the same techniques used by techno-capitalism as an approach to dramatize the data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Edward Ward</title>
      <link>/artists/edward-ward/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artists/edward-ward/</guid>
      <description>Edward Ward is an academic, artist and designer exploring speculative ecologies. His practice centres around the creation of physical artefacts that reflect current attitudes towards technology, ontologies, and the environment. Using a range of media and processes (organisms, programming, mechatronics). These works are realised to provoke discussion and inquiry within the field of post phenomenology and spatial practice.
His latest work explores the symbiotic relationship between algae, humans and technology; referencing the algae’s position in the systems of sensing, food politics and the Anthropocene.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eevi Rutanen</title>
      <link>/artists/eevi-rutanen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artists/eevi-rutanen/</guid>
      <description>In the work of Eevi Rutanen (b.1992, Finland), interactive installations, sculpture, and software merge into uncanny hybrids of bodies and technology. Drawing on her background in bioengineering, Eevi&amp;rsquo;s work is often inspired by biological processes and forms. By combining computational systems and scientific paradigms with frivolity and feminist theory, she strives to imagine alternative ways of being and knowing through empowered softness and sensuality. Eevi graduated with a BA in Graphic Design from Aalto University in 2016, and is currently finishing her MFA degree in Computational Arts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eirini Kalaitzidi</title>
      <link>/artists/eirini-kalaitzidi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artists/eirini-kalaitzidi/</guid>
      <description>Eirini Kalaitzidi is a dance artist who works with technology in order to generate poetic movement and shape spaces where mutually affective encounters of bodies emerge. As an alternative to choreographing, she is exploring a techno-feminist practise of being in a choreo-milieu, i.e. in the in-between human and non-human, physical and digital, static and dynamic dancing agencies. Eirini is intrigued by blending and layering materials, dimensions and moving behaviours for the purpose of creating fictional choreo-related events.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elina Virdzinience</title>
      <link>/artists/elina-virdzinience/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artists/elina-virdzinience/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elle Castle</title>
      <link>/artists/elle-castle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artists/elle-castle/</guid>
      <description>Elle Castle is a computational artist and creative technologist specialising in physical computing and robotics. Elle&amp;rsquo;s work is primarily concerned with disrupting fascist and eugenicist ideas relating to a &amp;ldquo;natural order&amp;rdquo;, as well as addressing issues relating to gendered violence, displacement and the occult. Her background is in domestic/gendered violence organising, martial arts/self defence, and the grinding misery of full-time administrative work. Elle currently works in the Creative Technology Lab at London College of Communication, UAL where she teaches physical computing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harry Morley</title>
      <link>/artists/harry-morley/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artists/harry-morley/</guid>
      <description>Harry Morley is a musician and computational artist with a background in jazz, popular music and sound design. His love of deep listening together with improvising, has led him to focus on using noise, silence, harmony and recorded sounds in his work.
Harry creates generative, ongoing systems as well as designing new ways to organise and visualise sounds using machine learning. He also explores the lives of inanimate objects and thinks about musical objects as creatures to influence and be influenced by.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Helena Wee</title>
      <link>/artists/helena-wee/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artists/helena-wee/</guid>
      <description>Helena utilises science, technology and her cultural background as a way of investigating hidden mental spaces, speculative worlds and the politics of knowledge production. Her recent work has encompassed climate injustices, Chinese five element theory, geotechnology and speculative fiction, linking them through Yuk Hui&amp;rsquo;s concept of a “moral cosmotechnics”. She examines new algorithmic paradigms and their effects on developmental, political and environmental realities through the lens of Qi, Dao and the I Ching.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Izzy McLellan</title>
      <link>/artists/izzy-mclellan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artists/izzy-mclellan/</guid>
      <description>Izzy McLellan is a computational artist with an academic background in Graphic Arts and Design. Her practice is increasingly guided by questions concerning what the terms craft and tradition encompass, in both an ancient and technological sense, and how fine the line is between nature and computation. On a material level these thoughts have guided a practice that heavily considers materiality and tools, the purpose of screens, and a crossover between ‘high’ and ‘low’ tech.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>James Tregaskis</title>
      <link>/artists/james-tregaskis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artists/james-tregaskis/</guid>
      <description>James Tregaskis’ work is concerned with the increased lack of privacy borne out of living in a neoliberal world accelerated by ubiquitous digital technologies. He explores strategies for surviving within systems of surveillance and control, and presents his research expressed through modified domestic surveillance apparatus of the past.
James’s passion for computing started at age 11, after attending the Cybernetic Serendipity exhibition at the ICA (1968). During his time working in advertising, he delivered his client the one of the world’s first colour portable computer in 1983 while working at Saatchi and Saatchi; then went on to continue his career in software development for the next 30 years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>John Dore</title>
      <link>/artists/john-dore/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artists/john-dore/</guid>
      <description>John Dore explores the relationship between the pursuit of knowledge and aesthetic gratification. Utilising methods and approaches rooted in computer science, biology, mathematics and philosophy. John’s work pivots on traversing unfamiliar territories for the sake of temporary illumination. At the core of his practice is the notion that if the purpose of visualization is insight, then perhaps it is through space, both afforded to and created by fleeting aesthetics, that our definitions of insight and understanding can be re-imagined.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Julia Creuheras</title>
      <link>/artists/julia-creuheras/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artists/julia-creuheras/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Julian Burgess</title>
      <link>/artists/julian-burgess/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artists/julian-burgess/</guid>
      <description>Julian is interested in underlying structures in computation and how they connect to nature and the physical world.
His background is as a JavaScript web engineer in news graphics and data visualisation working at Bloomberg, The Guardian and The Times.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Julien Mercier</title>
      <link>/artists/julien-mercier/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artists/julien-mercier/</guid>
      <description>Julien Mercier’s core topics of interest are ethics and accountability in Machine Learning, and cognitive processes such as self-perception and cognitive dissonance. His work ranges across installation, sound, and video, as following both material and conceptual concerns.
He assumes moving images as being replicas of reality, and as such finds it vital to understand them as fluid artefacts that promote immersive experiences. Recent advances in Deep Learning afford more dimensions than ever before: Julien explores the mystifying capacities of such technology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kata Popovic</title>
      <link>/artists/kata-popovic/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artists/kata-popovic/</guid>
      <description>Katarina Popovic - Kata is a storyteller and media artist. Her works explore the process of reintegrating humans back (to their imminent) nature through art and technology. She examines how humans interface with non-humans revealing deep, often invisible connections. This year Kata is focused on the &amp;lsquo;silent witnesses&amp;rsquo; concept – coined to describe the act of giving voice to natural elements and objects through electronics interventions and software. Kata is interested in how natural and cultural history can be experienced deeply, rather than just - seen or read about.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keita Ikeda</title>
      <link>/artists/keita-ikeda/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artists/keita-ikeda/</guid>
      <description>Keita Ikeda is a creative technologist working with light, physical materials and computer programming to explore visual perception, form and materiality. He seeks to design alternative mediums of artistic expression, and finds beauty not only in the content of a work, but in the very process of information materialising through a medium. He sees computation as a fundamental element in his practice, not merely as a tool but a material in its own right, like paint for a painter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Laura Traver</title>
      <link>/artists/laura-traver/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artists/laura-traver/</guid>
      <description>Laura is a computational and fine artist based in London. Her work is founded in her interest in the exploration of the creative process and preference to discover an outcome, rather than design or imagine one. She frequently creates constructive systems and rules that probe and alter her role as the artist and facilitate the creation of art. Laura&amp;rsquo;s work often bears evidence of her physical interaction and presence in the making of the piece, either through fast-paced, expressive gestures or controlled, focused mark-making.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Luke Dash</title>
      <link>/artists/luke-dash/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artists/luke-dash/</guid>
      <description>Luke Dash explores musical composition through software, their approach centered on the limitations of the minimal hardware which they take for a medium. Conceptually, the practice is motivated by a desire to interrogate notions of containment. The calculated placement of components across this system is owed to a desire to gently upset ideas of outer limits. Length of string gives body to sounds discovered during a longstanding practice experimenting with electronic instruments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nathan Bayliss</title>
      <link>/artists/nathan-bayliss/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artists/nathan-bayliss/</guid>
      <description>Nathan Bayliss interrogates technology that shapes the human experience. He asks how we may better understand the technologies that invisibly reconfigure contemporary life and how these technologies could be re-purposed to tell down to earth, personal stories. Working within a deconstructed documentary format, his recent films utilise machine learning to build models from the past to speculate on (im)possible futures. Born in Australia, Nathan Bayliss moved to London in 2008 and now works from a studio in Hackney, East London.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Owen Planchart</title>
      <link>/artists/owen-planchart/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artists/owen-planchart/</guid>
      <description>Owen Planchart is a creative technologist using the border between the digital and the analogue as his medium. In the past, his work ranged from interactive video-mapping to 3d-printed sculptures and robotised found objects. His current projects explore the cross-contamination of art forms such as puppetry, performance and light sculpture which has been referred to as a kind of silicon-dadaism, using a unique style of multimedia collage to provoke layered readings on the subjects of transformation, synesthesia and control.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Panja Göbel</title>
      <link>/artists/panja-g%C3%B6bel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artists/panja-g%C3%B6bel/</guid>
      <description>Panja’s artistic practice engages directly with the entangled human-machine relationships arising within the landscape of our current networked world. With a particular focus on experimental wearables and augmenting the body, she makes use of electronics, circuitry and custom interactive systems in order to create installations, wearable art and mixed reality experiences that aim to expose and often subvert their purpose.
Having worked for two decades in the design and tech industry, Panja is now using her previous knowledge to create speculative, thought-provoking pieces that aim to engage, disrupt and reconfigure our relationships with machines.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Petros Velousis</title>
      <link>/artists/petros-velousis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artists/petros-velousis/</guid>
      <description>Petros Velousis is an Athens-born, artist and creative technologist currently based in London. With a background in TV - theatre music composition, music production, and sound design, his work has been focusing on exploring new sonic possibilities and nontraditional approaches to musical practice.
His current art practices seek novel interpretations of sound and musical objects in responsive sound pieces and installations, aiming to question the way we interact with ourselves and with others, through our memories, as well as nature and the mechanical systems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rachel Max</title>
      <link>/artists/rachel-max/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artists/rachel-max/</guid>
      <description>Rachel is a designer and computational artist currently based in London. Her work utilizes digital and crafting platforms to create objects which question the non-transactional nature of technological interactions. Using humor and satire, her speculative and critical work delights, frustrates, and ultimately challenges assumptions and conceptions about the role that objects play in everyday life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Raphael Theolade</title>
      <link>/artists/raphael-theolade/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artists/raphael-theolade/</guid>
      <description>Raphael Theolade was born in France in 1987. He always has been fascinated by the individual and cultural perception of time and space and its synaesthetic manifestation through light, colour, movement and sound; as well as cultivating a vivid enthusiasm for late digital technologies. These interests were developed when he opted to take his 3D Animation Direction Degree in Supinfocom in Valenciennes (France) from 2007 to 2012.
After completing his degree, Raphael got involved in the animation industry, working for several projects such as features, series, music videos or commercials in various studios across Europe, including Cartoon Network and Passion Pictures.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rebecca Aston</title>
      <link>/artists/rebecca-aston/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artists/rebecca-aston/</guid>
      <description>Rebecca Aston is a Zimbabwean artist currently based in London. Her work explores the material culture. She questions and decodes the meaning embedded in physical and virtual spaces, objects and the environment. Reflecting on post-colonialism, she examines global flows of data, matter and people, throughout history, up until the present day, to speculate on new futures. Temporality is central to her practice both as a subject matter and medium through which she explores history and memories by means of capture technologies, computation and the moving image.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Richard Moores</title>
      <link>/artists/richard-moores/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artists/richard-moores/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sarah Song Xiaran</title>
      <link>/artists/sarah-song-xiaran/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artists/sarah-song-xiaran/</guid>
      <description>Sarah Song is a new media artist currently based in London. Her practice lies at the junction of the natural world, sound, as well as visuals. She works in a variety of media and most of her artworks aim to explore the creative relationships and possibilities between nature and digital technology and to find poetic meaning in one&amp;rsquo;s daily life. Always fascinated by the macroscopic world, the concepts of minimalism and surrealism.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shuai Xu</title>
      <link>/artists/shuai-xu/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artists/shuai-xu/</guid>
      <description>Shuai Xu is a creative coder and new media artist currently based in London. Since 2016, Shuai has been focused on digital media art, technology, and science. His recent work bridged the conversation between traditional Narration language and algorithmic machine, exploring the relationship between immersive environment and interactive systems. In this way, the search for digital technology and Narration expression may be able to go beyond independent feeling, potentially creating new relationships between body, environment, and technology, as well as new ways to bring aesthetic consciousness among people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taoran Xu</title>
      <link>/artists/taoran-xu/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artists/taoran-xu/</guid>
      <description>Taoran Xu (China, 1993) is active as a computational artist and sonic interactive designer. His works explore states wherein digital, analog signals and technology intertwine and merge into hybrid sonic units. The origins of his works follow a line of research into field recordings and soundwalks, soundscape ecology and the immersive potential of spatial sound and sensorial potential of technology. His installation works immerse the audience and construct new realities, manifesting through multi-channel projection and dynamic binaural experiences.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teodora Sinziana Fartan</title>
      <link>/artists/teodora-sinziana-fartan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artists/teodora-sinziana-fartan/</guid>
      <description>Teodora Sinziana Fartan is an artist, writer and creative technologist based in London, UK. Her art practice investigates new modes of experience and methods for generating alternate imaginaries through the use of speculation, fictioning and deconstructed Narrations as thought-making tools for imagining beyond our current accelerationist climate and its progressively apparent flaws. With a focus on fiction production as critical practice, Teodora’s work often draws on science fiction, natural phenomena, literary techniques, mythology, ritual practices, cosmological perspectives and futurology in its attempt to seek what can exist beyond our increasingly computationally-driven social, political, environmental and existential context.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Valeria Radchenko</title>
      <link>/artists/valeria-radchenko/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artists/valeria-radchenko/</guid>
      <description>Valeria Radchenko is a multi-disciplinary artist whose work is, at its core, concerned with connection in the information age, and vibration as sound, as affect, as embodied states. Working mainly with video, performance and sound, they explore the micro/macro relationship between personal Narrations and wider patterns and cycles of life. More generally - investigating what it means to be human by looking at our relationship with nature, technology, each other and our own selves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yiyan Lin</title>
      <link>/artists/yiyan-lin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artists/yiyan-lin/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yunjeong Jang (Yuni)</title>
      <link>/artists/yunjeong-jang-yuni/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artists/yunjeong-jang-yuni/</guid>
      <description>Yunjeong Jang (Yuni) was born in Busan (1993), developed her career in Seoul and is currently based in London. From childhood, she was surrounded by novel technologies and engineering practices. This has left a strong impact on the aesthetic development of her art practice. In digital art, she praises the utopian harmony between organic and machinery. Furthermore, Yuni provides an approach that examines how binary matters can be combined, such as living with non-living, organic and inorganic, human and non-human with the development of technology and science.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ziwei Wu</title>
      <link>/artists/ziwei-wu/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artists/ziwei-wu/</guid>
      <description>Ziwei Wu was born in Shenzhen, China, in 1996. She studies and lives in London, UK. Wu’s artworks are mainly based on biology, science and their influence on society. She uses a range of media including painting, installation, audio-visual, 2D and 3D animations, VR, and projection mapping. In 2018 she won the Lumen Prize’s Meural Student Award for her sonic installation artwork “The Punishment of Tantalus”.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>